[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ and informative email subject line is very helpful, whereas one that is too vague or too long can get your email mistaken for something unimportant.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Of course she makes grammar mistakes; she is at the ____ stage of learning English.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He said the debate now should ____ events of the past and the focus should be on what the UN, the US and Iraq could do to achieve the results.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The terrorist plane crashing into the New York tower is an ____ that most people will never forget.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people believe that the invasion of Iraq was a ____ mistake.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They are never forgotten, those brief moments of splendid ____ sandwiched between so many slices of rancid defeat.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "victory", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company won the ____ to supply the government with 30,000 special computers for primary schools.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your composition must ____ an introduction, a conclusion and three body paragraphs.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "revise", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But mine was not a ____ Negro family. My grandmother never took in washing or worked in service or went much to church.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in order to ____ his political survival.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "assure", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning technique to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Professor Cowen has a ____ interest in professional service firms and has conducted much of her research in the investment banking industry.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her grades will start to ____ unless she cuts back on the number of after-school activities she does.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your book. Did your dog try to eat it?", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students should discuss ____ options with their academic advisor.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Every employee must ____ an annual tax declaration to his or her local tax office.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "submit", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most serious ____ to implementing the Convention in Venezuela was clearly the poverty facing a large proportion of the population.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "obstacle", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Stated simply, this ____ means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks approximately like any other part.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "access", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "the right to enter or use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If your ____ is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and contact the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most significant ____ factor in predicting whether a person will commit a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new factory near the school will ____ parts for mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Political Bureau will work to ensure the smooth ____ of the reform of the administrative system.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She has a ____ in one eye that makes it difficult for her to read from the board.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She has massive problems with her spelling. There was ____ a word she got right in the dictation.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is often necessary to ____ a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies demonstrate that the state was not able to ____ discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Corms have shapes similar to bulbs, but do not ____ fleshy scales.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The pattern of weight change through pregnancy was ____ across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The soldier shot the dog for no ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The topic of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could ____ fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The students had to ____ the planned class picnic when the day started with heavy rain and wind.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While I don't present this as ____ the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is of ____ importance that you learn academic vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "D. perceives this as deviation from what she considers the traditional ____ of behaviour of Greek women.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "impulse", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "code", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Giuliani's leadership during New York City's darkest hours of the September 11th terrorist attacks earned him global ____ and admiration.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please ____ the missing information before submitting the form, otherwise it will be returned to you to complete.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not ____ the dots.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Because multicultural audiences will likely become more and more common, you will need to ____ cultural differences when you analyze your audience.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "anticipate", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to expect", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Aqaba ____ (see fig. 11.6) would pump sea water during off-peak periods.", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even with support, because of his health and limits on the hours he could work, he was unable to fulfill the duties of the ____ teaching job.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Is the Smartboard just the latest teaching ____ that will be popular for a year or so and then disappear without trace?", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "German Liberals had tried and failed to ____ Germany during the Revolution of 1848.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "aid", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "help (often financial help)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You must ____ copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should highlight the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sometimes it is difficult to find the ____ word to convey an idea. This is particularly true if you are speaking in your second language.", "Opt_1": "averse", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "against", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Developments in computer technology may ____ make accurate weather forecasting possible.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Since that time two major surveys were conducted with an attempt to define the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to ____ your work a little more closely for silly spelling or punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Next you need to ____ a search statement so you can conduct a database search.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The unpleasant ____ in the computer lab is sure to occupy my thoughts in the next few days.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Once the conference is over the government will turn its ____ to the problems of urban crime.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This paper documents ____ findings from a nationwide survey that investigates substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Economics is the allocation of ____ resources among competing ends.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some students find it difficult to ____ to a new school in a new country.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices gradually decreased until ____ zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must ____ instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions suppress the need for communication or being able to freely ____ your emotions?", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is to the government's credit that they refused to ____ in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a ____ of meaning in the story that you have not written about.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ problem facing the world this century is how to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "elementary", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ why he made such a foolish decision.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Candidates must ____ a high level of responsibility, the ability to work independently, and a strong commitment to customer service.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Banks that ____ the Equator Principles apply them globally to project financing in all industry sectors including mining, oil and gas, and forestry.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "propose", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A major problem for most western societies is how to ____ immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She found that the document had no detail and conflicted with the assessments of ____ intelligence.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A verbal contract is impossible to prove, and the organization will always ____ that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "At first there was a little ____ between the Japanese and Korean students, but this soon passed.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is largely responsible for the ____ of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was a tough decision, but ultimately I think it was the student life that had the greatest ____ on my decision to come to Wheaton.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She resisted the ____ pressure to take a husband because she regarded marriage as fundamentally incompatible with the objectives of her reign.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is a fact that ____ drivers have fewer accidents than reckless ones.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The director planned to ____ the information to the workforce at the next general assembly.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must ____ against the firms from not merely India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The communication ____ is a computer, phone line, and modem; the student must have access to the necessary equipment.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A three-year Indian bachelor's degree is NOT ____ to a U.S. bachelor's degree.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Flights from Athens to the island are on small planes which fill up quickly; they are not very ____ and are often booked several months in advance.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Banks that ____ the Equator Principles apply them globally to project financing in all industry sectors including mining, oil and gas, and forestry.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As a result of the rise in the price of oil, the government has decided not to ____ the proposed tax increase.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My teacher will not let me sit near to John any more. She says he is a bad ____ on me.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to ____ in school you will have to study hard!", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The house was built so carelessly that it began to fall ____ after only a couple of years.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, ____ in the case of an independent investigation.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They have other business interests to which they ____ their attention, and they may be expected to continue to do so.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An important clue to understanding volcanoes is knowing the ____ of the volcanic bands.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The water ____ is one of the natural processes that are familiar to most students.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many undergraduates have little ____ in organizing tasks and making good use of time.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Janice Walker wanted to examine further ways to continue this great benefit to the company's ____ as well as the company's productivity.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must ____ the following requirements each semester in order to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not ____ the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Hacking's book suffers from a serious defect, ____ he does not understand the nature of hypnosis.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The father stated he was from the neighbourhood of Bandon, where he had been unable to ____ any employment.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ responsibility of a teacher is to teach.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is too early to make an ____ diagnosis of her problems in learning English.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law ____ to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although his letter did not ____ Atlanta as the location of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "stipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not ____ enough to identify exactly the minimum that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Instead of quick results, Cronbach (1963) believed that consistent experiences ____ improve performance over time.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "symptom", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Ambition was not an ____ of the female characters in his earlier films.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not ____ the dots.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most historians agree that Kievan Russia was not a ____ political, cultural, or ethnic entity.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I tried to ____ the information on the internet, but could find nothing useful.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As maintenance requirements and costs increase, fewer aircraft will be in a ____ state of readiness or mission-capable.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While the Spartans were principally responsible for the victory, the Athenian fleet was probably the most important ____ of that victory.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most have concluded that no logic of discovery exists and, moreover, that a ____ model of discovery is impossible.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ version of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company's ____ for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We do not yet know the ____ for the government of the rapid rise in house prices.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The mask must always ____ the actor in expressing both joy and grief.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "survive", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to not die", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government will ____ in the coming election how unpopular its politics have been.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Supervisors must ____ employees in the importance of safe work practices.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "However, as a dermatologist I felt the articles did not ____ strongly enough the possible drawbacks of the treatment.", "Opt_1": "dedicate", "Opt_2": "stress", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_2_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We all have to tolerate differences of ____ in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small ____ was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The cakes ____ of flour, sugar, eggs and milk.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She has no means of studying in peace at home. Her ____ life is too chaotic.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government is thinking about introducing courses to ____ young people how to be good parents.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The media and the public should not ____ the music industry for the jobs that parents are not fulfilling.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A ____ teaching methodology will not be successful in a class with many different nationalities and abilities.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Based on his research, Healey developed a system that combined the display of multiple values into a single ____ element.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "\"We hope to ____ the historic value of these buildings and encourage serious parties to step", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually ____ exceptional performance remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to consider requiring the student to ____ from the College.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to ____ food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was expelled from school for a ____ attempt to cheat in the end of year exams.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The different religious groups ____ came to realize that none of them could hope to prevail over all the others.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly ____ graduate students.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Another reason to ____ student e-mail and internet usage is to ensure their safety.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ your good mood if it's hot and loud in the classroom, you have a headache, and the work is very boring.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One crucial reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in ____ productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her poor behaviour, but promised never to repeat it.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ your feet from the table! People have to eat here!", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "remove", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to take away", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please ____ your disk, shut the disk drive and then click on 'Save'.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "donate", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He started searching for evidence of Wilson's existence and ____ succeeded in documenting her life up to 1863.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In fact, the price of ____ is \ufffd\ufffd5000 higher if it lies in a section with the Mississippi river passing.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In this assignment, you will need to ____ an array of numbers, so that your computer code executes correctly.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is a ____ in my family for everyone to get together for Sunday lunch.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Roman Catholic Church along with the main Protestant denominations in Europe did not ____ the slave trade.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Performance in the money markets has been consistent in recent months, but prices are expected to ____ in the near future.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government has changed its ____ to nuclear power now that the cost of oil has been so high for the past few years.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company made a radical reduction in its workforce in order to improve its ____ in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students will learn to ____ what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an outcome are associated.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production process may be reduced if a sufficiently large ____ is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are applying from a country in which English is not the ____ language, you are required to submit evidence of English language proficiency.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has only had ____ success in reducing the number of unemployed people.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government was unable to ____ that it was considering invading North Korea.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Ask the candidate to ____ what they believe to have been their most significant challenges and accomplishments in their current job or a previous job.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher made the ____ decision to take her class out to the playground and finish the lesson there.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "voluntary", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different ____ of the incident than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar symbol of ____ to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a business person who frequently deals with recent college graduates, I'd say that there has been a ____ deterioration of writing (and speaking) skills.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "rare", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "unusual", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My overall impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically ____ manner.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government ____ did not take steps to investigate or punish the most serious cases of abuse.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Children visiting the internet chatrooms are advised not to ____ their real names.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is our belief that the students were not given a fair hearing, and ____ that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "furthermore", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I was unable to ____ the reason for Angelica's sudden departure at the beginning of the second trimester.", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "undertake", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To accurately determine mass balance, stakes were placed in the ____ clean ice areas of the glacier.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An ____ of this war is the rise of a large anti-war movement in the US.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "result"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most serious problems that ____ the new government.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a ____ reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students, ____ and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to disrupt classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "stage", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Thanks to the ____ description of the witnesses, the police were able to identify the bank robbers.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of the students' time is spent performing experiments, with required one-on-one mentorship by a graduate student, fellow, or faculty member.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was ____ the most significant function of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Politics is still a ____ male profession.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "very"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the attempt was an ____ failure.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "While a considerable ____ of agreement was attained, a uniform approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "degree", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The unit did not ____ nuclear weapons in as much detail as some of my students would have liked.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to ____ his concept against the competitive approach favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The new economies of Chile and Costa Rica have little ____ for poor, unskilled and uneducated workers.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "specify", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to state exactly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ to accept the idea that man is mere flotsam and jetsam in the river of life, unable to influence the unfolding events which surround him.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't think the government will manage to ____ many people to recycle more of their garbage.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unfortunately NIH did not ____ the funding request.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Stated simply, this principle means that averaged over large enough distances, one part of the Universe looks ____ like any other part.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "likely", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "probable", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Such web content does not necessarily ____ the opinions of the University administration.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "involve", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to include or mean"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since you have not attended class for the last seven weeks, I ____ that you are not interested in graduating.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The population of a country will ____ if more people die than are born.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Successful applicants will have to provide evidence of medical insurance for the ____ of their stay in the Ukraine.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The world's largest film ____ is in Hollywood, Los Angeles.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In many cases, ____ stating to the student that the behavior is unacceptable and must not occur again is sufficient.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the political support needed to maintain funding for the integrated ____ program.", "Opt_1": "lecture", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company is selecting the best of ____ names that have been suggested for its new product.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even though the South voted solidly against Lincoln, they could not ____ his victory.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "APA offers specific recommendations for eliminating ____ in language concerning race, disability, and sexuality.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will not prevail unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to ____ in public service.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "repeat", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The explanation for this extraordinary decision lies in the immediate ____ surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the principal decided not to ____ their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The student's answer may not address all parts of the question or may demonstrate an inaccurate or ____ analysis of the passage.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to ____ the progress of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and ____ decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Requiring students to leave the school building at lunchtime is not a very popular ____ from the new principal.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The results from this experimental course ____ very clearly that flow visualization can be performed successfully by a wide range of people.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students need to ____ with the department offering the master's degree to ensure the correct credential courses are taken.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This section is not an ____ to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity explore topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to ____ and coordinate their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to ____ a variety of materials to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In some businesses it is the ____ that the eldest son takes over when the father dies.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will ____ unless we delay our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In future we will increasingly need to ____ wind and sun power as fossil fuels such as coal and oil become more expensive.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you offend ____ the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Be warned: Becoming a parent will ____ many sleepless nights and a house full of plastic toys.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Research into heart disease has revealed a clear pattern: those who smoke too much, drink too much and do not ____ enough are the most likely to suffer from it.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an evident ____ that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Individual investors: ____ with caution.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a minimum ____ for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "duration", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are ____ any teachers at the school who cannot speak at least two languages.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ your good mood if it's hot and loud in the classroom, you have a headache, and the work is very boring.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must devise a plan to ____ greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The business will not ____ unless it can win new customers in foreign countries.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to assimilate the material covered by the homework problems in ____ to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "order", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "sequence, place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have enormous difficulty understanding certain sentences that ____ common sense.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is yet another ____ example of the positive partnership between TMH and the FSU College of Medicine.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The tale ends with Gilgamesh, at the end of his ____ standing before the gates of Uruk.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "degree", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "journey", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The study included a diagram of the ____ concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Just follow the on-screen instructions as you ____ the discussion forum from within a course.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are ____ of things that the new government needs to change when it comes into power.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have made no effort to learn, ____ you will not be entered for the test.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to trust your ____ as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Which do you ____ the more: health or wealth?", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A records check was unable to verify his claim that he possessed a ____ license.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Groups should advise the instructor if a ____ is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A Parisian mob broke into the palace killing many of the guards, while searching for the ____ family.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students should discuss ____ options with their academic advisor.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They did not ____ an attack. They responded to an attack from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If a student is caught with drugs in the building, the school will ____ him or her.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable ____ to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you want to run this software, you will need to ____ the operating system.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How can I ____ access to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "contemplate", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to think about; to consider"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In closing, I want to assert that I know that our ____ is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is really no point in arguing which ____ is better.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some organizations have tried to ____ without a clear hierarchy, but in most cases people want to know who their boss is.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Poor results in end of year tests often ____ that the teacher has not taught the course very well.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously affect your ____ grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "general"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Despite the fact that there was a stream on the land, he could not ____ of the property at any price.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to reveal the secret until means have been ____ to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is often necessary to ____ a complex set of \"metadata\" with each data point in order to make that datum useful.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ a student of plagiarism, you must have strong evidence.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more ____ tasks.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to ____ energy and help contribute to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to develop methods to ____ a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Samuel Huang, a professor of chemistry and materials science, has created an ____ tendon out of biodegradable materials.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not really her ____ that she comes late to school so often. She lives a long way away, and often gets stuck in a traffic jam.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the aid money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When they did investigations after 9-11, one of the major things that they came up with was that the various government agencies did not ____ the dots.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science block ____ the sports field.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually ____ exceptional performance remain out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the next 50 years the world's weather could ____ significantly if the polar ice continues to melt.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He was not ____ to retreat from previous legal commitments.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In recognition of your continuous ____ service to the university, you will receive an award at five-year intervals.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "remote", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "far, distant, small"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some parents or guardians who place their children temporarily in foster care do so because they cannot ____ their abilities to raise their children.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "territory", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to illustrate how the ____ works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Due to the recent increase in student numbers, the school can now ____ to build a new science laboratory.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most educational institutions have a required ____ for citations and references.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "account", "Answer": "format", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I speculate that she will not be given a ____ job at the school.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "permanent", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The secret September 2002 Pentagon intelligence report concluded that there was \"no ____ information\" that Iraq had biological or chemical weapons.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The head teacher could not assure parents that there would be no ____ in school fees.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has two problems; ____ his inability to concentrate in class and his unwillingness to do homework.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that random is ____ the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ that difficulties at home underlie her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The house was built so carelessly that it began to fall ____ after only a couple of years.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "related", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "connected; having something to do with each other"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For many persons these are not ____ concerns but profound and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another layer to an already ____ decision -making process.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over 100 students marched to the Hoover Institution to ____ a possible U.S. war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher said that he could not ____ to grade all the papers by the next lesson.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can buy each ____ on the school supplies list from the bookstore.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "item", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "thing, element"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teacher trainees will need to master problem-solving strategies that ____ clear practical solutions to issues that affect those in poverty.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to ____ methods to produce a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was not the ____ of going to school; it was expected that you'd go to work and contribute to the family.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Education has reduced the ____ at which the disease has spread throughout the population.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Remember that more than one ____ may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often overlap in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Princeton University computer scientist Edward Felton has decided not to ____ a paper on how his research team broke the code of copyright protection.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is an activity in which I expect you to work together. Do not try to ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not enough to ____ children not to play with fireworks. It should be illegal for children to buy them.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is to the government's ____ that they refused to participate in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "belief", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A major defect in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The immigrants probably did not ____ more than ten per cent of the population.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She chose to reject the ____ that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Car companies spend a ____ sum of money advertising their products.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a ____ transition.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "fare", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He uses Blanche White to ____ the problems of color and class difference between blacks and whites.", "Opt_1": "persist", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "forego", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Miller, long a ____ of Switzerland, broke with the school of traditional psychoanalysis over the issue.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to receive a ____ investigation and review should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please remember to inspect any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other ____ to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "attend", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to go to, to be present at"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People today have become more ____ of their individual responsibility to protect the environment.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "approve", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to agree to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't know how I always ____ to get such a good grade. I never work particularly hard.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He also was able to ____ in identifying outstanding science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many schools in poorer parts of the world do not have ____ books and computers to give their students a good education.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will gain no ____ for work that has simply been copied from the internet.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Design your syllabus so that it communicates to students what you expect them to learn and also how to ____ in achieving the learning goals for your course.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Color did not ____ the perceived sweetness of the drink and did not ____ the drink's ability to quench thirst.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Thorough cleaning must always ____ chemical disinfection of any equipment.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is an activity in which I expect you to work together. Do not try to ____ with each other.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "establish", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to begin or set up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A hunt for hazardous asteroids by University of Hawaii astronomers who use a unique search ____ has paid off.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company is selecting the best of ____ names that have been suggested for its new product.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "sole", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "only"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The links between ____ price declines and food prices are not easy to discern.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "margin", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "amount; distance"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not an ____ solution by any means, as it limits researchers to a small percentage of the information they could gain from these archives.", "Opt_1": "superficial", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking harsh actions ____ communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are in ____ pain you should consult a doctor.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The two teams are ____ equal. It's difficult to predict who is going to win.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Only 45% passed the ____ examination. That is not a very impressive statistic.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government survey produced a wide ____ of responses.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "range", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some families who emigrate to Germany are surprised at the ____ of sweeping the street in front of your house every Saturday morning.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "authority", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "custom", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is generally not a ____ decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "considerable", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no ____ of an original idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Muscles ____ unless they are exercised; just like the brain!", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her ____ absence from school is the principal reason for her bad grades in the final exams.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The primary ____ of the Management Information Systems Department is to prepare students for exciting and challenging careers in the information technology.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is hardly a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He alleged that the state had adopted the policy of attacking the entire independent media ____ than targeting individual journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ that spider from the box. It will die if you keep it in there.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "release", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a ____ basis to incorporate new understanding.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He did not manage to ____ a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "organize", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "China did not ____ nuclear weapons. Having produced several hundred warheads, China stopped building up its military potential.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an inevitable ____ of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In the long run, democratic market capitalism has proved superior to deterministic, ____ socialism.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "His idea is ____ not feasible - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Good teachers must ____ their students as they find them, as they present themselves, walking in the door.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "China has experienced dynamic ____ in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Follow these recommended times for storage in the freezer to enjoy the best quality in flavor and texture and to ____ good nutritive value.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Sitting too long in front of a computer may ____ headaches or back problems.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She ignored an ____ warning that she would be expelled if she did not start working harder.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Nowadays, knowledge is viewed as a significant ____ for organizations.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "asset", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Samuel Huang, a professor of chemistry and materials science, has created an ____ tendon out of biodegradable materials.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, in those studies, he was unable to ____ the campaign's effectiveness in reaching the people of Uganda.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We are going to ____ this photograph to poster size and put it on the classroom wall.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The goal is to ____ world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and service within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "attitude", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The student was ____ active with the experiment and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Bassett did not ____ to take on responsibilities outside the classroom.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Victims of terrorist attacks are usually given ____ by the government.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "extremely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "very"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as ____ and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Dr. Carpenter told the jury that Hinckley was unable to ____ reality from fiction.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this magnitude will ____ the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As incoming college students have arrived, I've compiled a list of all the truly important things that you need to have to ____ this experience.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "While I don't present this as ____ the ultimate method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "formula", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A headache may seem like a ____ problem, but it could be the sign of something more serious.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "familiar", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Since we can't ____ it directly, we need to infer it from the things we can ____.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The teacher thought about the best opportunity to ____ that she was leaving to have a baby.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a ____ of meaning in the story that you have not written about.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "topic", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or discussion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Typical conversations ____ a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans accumulate as they grow.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her sadness when she only came third in the music competition.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "According to him migrants and refugees do not ____ enough in Dutch society.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's no use trying to ____ me that your father speaks 10 languages. I just don't believe you.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is unpopular and is expected to ____ badly in the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The company directors are ____ that business will improve in the new year.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From the beginning he has shown a ____ attitude to being in Germany and learning the German language.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One danger of any powerful ____ is that, at the height of its power, people confuse the ____ and the thing that is being compared to it.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ problem facing the world this century is how to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He ____ failed to mention the unfortunate fact that he had dropped out of college.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is our belief that the students were not given a fair hearing, and ____ that the punishment was unjust.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "furthermore", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I don't believe that the government's plan to imprison more criminals is the best ____ for the problem of rising crime.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "display", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you wish to ____ at this school, you will have to conform to its rules.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My parents ____ a lot of money from their investments in internet companies.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Emma was conscious of these ____ and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She was making a ____ distinction between causing something and making something happen.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She will ____ reduce her chances of success if she continues to drink so much.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your final writing must ____ to your research notes, otherwise you risk being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the individual knows in advance when he or she wishes to ____ for time away from the workplace, the individual should complete the preliminary request form.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "No wonder your computer doesn't work. You must ____ it to the monitor!", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He has made substantial ____ this trimester.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first ____ on the agenda is the proposal to increase working hours to 42 per work.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Even very low temperatures do not ____ the strength of this material.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "retreat", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to go back"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The nurse gave me a ____ for my headache.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore apart a nation and created many social problems that did not ____ before its invention.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There are strict laws that ____ the trade in rainforest wood.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to dedicate herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to ____ serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can't always control what happens to you, but you can always control how you ____ to what happens to you.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has a ____ of everyone who has travelled to Afghanistan in the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would ____ an automatic decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an ____ number will always yield an even number.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer ____ a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When I typed in the ____ 'English as a Second Language' in Google, I got more than 20 million hits. That's a huge figure.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has set the ambitious ____ of halving child poverty by the year 2020.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In most of Africa, for example, weaker institutions have failed to impose restrictions on rulers and undemocratic ____ politics has been employed.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The student was reported to the headmaster for continually trying to ____ the class.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As yet there has been no ____ example of the sighting of a spacecraft from another world.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to ____ to a speed of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, especially in the case of an ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ the material covered by the homework problems in order to pass the quizzes and final examination.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's no surprise that she is so quiet in class. She can ____ speak a word of English.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There has been a recent ____ in language teaching towards more grammar and vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Doctors usually ____ patients to have some proof of ability to pay for treatment.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "accuse", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to blame", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "California's medical schools and major teaching hospitals are directly and ____ responsible for more than 200000 full-time jobs.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists devise a new way to ____ gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "deliver", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is often impossible to ____ the pronunciation of a word from its spelling alone.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "infer", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Do not ____ the period after an abbreviation such as in. (for inch), which could be confused with the word in.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "omit", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The doctor's ____ was pure hypocrisy. He more interested in making money than his patient's health.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you wish to ____ material that is copyrighted by someone besides yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are unable to attend a class for any reason, and would ____ to work directly from the student guide, please contact the Training Coordinator.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The results ____ that the best models will almost always incorporate both vertical and horizontal processes.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They all use tools from well outside the natural ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do you ever feel like some Asian traditions ____ the need for communication or being able to freely display your emotions?", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When questioned by the instructor, the student was unable to explain ____ of the terms and phrases he had used in his writing.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "abstract", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The University may terminate the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written ____ to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students engaging in scheduled curricular work have ____ over other students.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It can take as much as a ____ or more of hard study in a foreign language to become as fluent as a native speaker of that language.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unless we ____ the trend, the consequence will be a sustained contraction in the number and quality of staff scientists and research faculty.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He both provided a message service and the apparatus needed to send and ____ wireless messages.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Using a computer program makes it easier to ____ long pieces of writing.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "By reason of the duress of ____ disease, he has so far lost the power to choose between right and wrong.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and ____ of cities and ways planners solve urban problems.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "procedure", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We can conclude that China is unlikely to put significant pressure on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily ____ such pressure.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some students will insist that advertising does not \"mean\" anything; they may feel that ads have little ____ on the way people think and act.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I'm not sure he understands the ____ of the project. He will need to spend at least two hours on it every day for the next 3 weeks.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting threaten to ____ water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to enlarge the amount of land ____ for pasture.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not survive without support.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not all the decisions of the ____ have been welcomed by the workers.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their ____ whether it is safe to accept a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His research helped ____ that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on context and condition.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is ____ to lose students if the government goes ahead with its proposed legislation to reduce tax benefits for parents.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "loose", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Soviet nationality studies ____ that the state was not able to eliminate discrimination based on ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She found that the document had no ____ and conflicted with the assessments of military intelligence.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is NOT a reliable statistic and you should ____ ignore it.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was little ____ to the government's proposals to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the ____ format for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you work harder, you will ____ a better grade next term.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The proposed changes to the new law will ____ it of all its power.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ come to school by bus, but my father is driving me this week.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is ____ considered a pioneer in this field, both in conducting research and in educating students to assume key positions in industry.", "Opt_1": "dramatically", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When societies ____ into violence the result is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student enrolled in these types of courses really didn't get to know the instructor well and ____ did not feel any sense of community.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "conceal", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to hide", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a list of the local doctors who can speak English.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Internet is an ____ useful tool to look for housing, shops, restaurants, etc.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The naval and air forces failed to ____ their schedules and the carrier planes arrived a half hour later than expected.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ is to find the right mixture of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The precise answer is not at all straightforward, unless the uncertainty itself is related in a particular way to the ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities interact so ____ as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has recently published reports about farming in the UK and illegal drug-taking. The ____ has created far more interest in the media.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The paper was unable to ____ sufficient support and ceased publication after a few months.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a ____ of toilets in the school. Every time I want to use one, it is occupied.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After Iraq some people feel strongly that the USA should never again ____ in the affairs of other countries.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The course is aimed to develop appropriate skills and will therefore ____ to identify contexts where a traditional lecture might be required.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The unemployment figures ____ that the recent changes in tax have been successful.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some people claim that the ____ of the internet has been to the detriment of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The management is hoping that its new improved product will ____ increased profits.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Sports events such as the World Cup or the Olympic Games often culminate in an ____ firework display.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She is going to fail the course unless there is a ____ improvement in her efforts.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The role of doctors as a conscience of the ____ deserves more consideration in times of stress and under difficult circumstances such as war.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they simply did not ____ to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a ____ standard for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Yet Bush also has adopted other, more ____ policy positions on guns and gun control.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not obey a police order to ____ and was shot.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to exert force in order to ____ peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You must append copies of the primary literature that you are citing to your paper, and you should ____ the pertinent sections.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My father has a workshop in the garage so I have a lot of ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She has a ____ in one eye that makes it difficult for her to read from the board.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Science should be about ____ facts, not subjective opinions.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Each year the school has to ____ many of its textbooks from the USA or England-Germany needs to ____ more qualified computer technicians. It has failed to train enough of its own.", "Opt_1": "import", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of the new science building is not finished yet, but from the outside it looks great!", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "attribute", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the ____ with a valid excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You ____ yourself to unnecessary danger if you drive a car without wearing a seat belt.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "invest", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Further analysis suggested that the ____ was worse for women than men.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher decided to ____ the activity when it became clear that the students didn't understand what to do.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's good that the school employs employ new, young teachers every year. They can ____ discussions about teaching methods.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If he was ____ employed by the Grand Duke, that would account for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you do not ____ to the rules of the school, you will be asked to leave.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "isolate", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you ____ the figures carefully, you will see some strong patterns.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This survey examines attitudes ____ the campus-area housing market.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our ____ problem is how to convince the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Professor Cowen has a particular interest in professional service firms and has conducted much of her ____ in the investment banking industry.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The temperatures did not ____ as much this month as they did last month.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "fluctuate", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "fluctuate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors have not been able to establish the ____ cause of the patient's illness.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Blair will need to ____ the Americans that Europeans will no longer permit Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "But the mice did not ____ thorough cognitive testing, which requires intact mobility to navigate various mazes.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mr. Bush cannot answer Sheehan's question and he cannot ____ the war of aggression against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to settle the ____ between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As long as the person did not ____ large amounts of protein and carbohydrates, the effect on fat digestion was negated.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "consume", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This course traces the ____ concept of the hero by reading selected works by authors such as Homer, Plutarch and Caesar,", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying ____ science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial crisis and the Church was unable to ____ many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During this course you will review your knowledge of German, by focusing on the four language skills, ____ speaking, listening, reading and writing.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Simply exporting ____ graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a demand for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "surplus", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you want to ____ what is happening in Afghanistan, it is necessary to go there yourself.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "layer", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "level", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In closing, I want to ____ that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the bold and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "convey", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the ____ to improve his rather poor grades.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is will continue to undergo problems in its attempt to ____ new students unless it reduces its tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee ____ announced his intention to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Despite the overall satisfaction that the program was ____ successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ the methods and texts advocated by these educators with the powerful ideas of the critical pedagogues shaping his opinions.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an ____ war, trying to conceal the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug abuse underlie many ____ health problems.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because of their behavior in protecting food sources, it is ____ unusual to see two hummingbirds spending time together.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "so"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government should ____ making promises that it cannot keep.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has become unpopular recently and is ____ to lose the coming election.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "random", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "structure", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "exceed", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main ____ of a good teacher is knowledge of his or her subject.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "attribute", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you ____ the page, you will see the map I would like you to copy.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He was a visual thinker and an artist, albeit a ____ unsuccessful one.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "moreover", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His problems are ____ due to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But he did not ____ himself to theoretical matters alone. He now drew attention to the lack of American minority students on campus.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is one of several errors that ____ that your account is not set up properly; this can be corrected only by University personnel.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents communicate by email, but they cannot ____ on it.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that ____ is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most car companies are putting money into research into ____ forms of fuel. It will take a number of years, however, before anyone can develop a car that runs on water.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The headmaster was unable to ____ his proposal to lengthen the school day.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "improve", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "measure", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to find out how much there is of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some steps you can take to ____ yourself and your property are: Lock your room when sleeping and when you leave your room.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I thoroughly ____ this book to anybody interest in the vegetation of North America and to those studying similar vegetation in other parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "fail", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These facilities and supporting resources have been developed and are maintained at considerable ____ to the University and to the taxpayers of the State.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "expense", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "expense", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "cost", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Simply exporting ____ graduates is not itself a policy problem if there is a demand for those graduates.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "surplus", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Until 30 years ago, this was not a ____ problem because most could work in the agricultural and industrial economies of the day with little education.", "Opt_1": "feasible", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "possible", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is my firm intention to ____ with my department for at least two years.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We must be ____ in how we interpret the data. It would be easy to draw false conclusions.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "poor", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They are quoted at length in Kornbluh's book, The Pinochet File, and ____ cited in the New York Times.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "By running these ads, the newspaper is sending the message that it considers this a ____ product to sell.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "available", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The decision to make cannabis legal in small amounts is a significant ____ in the government's policy.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These notes are intended as a ____ introduction to some of the main ideas and methods of calculus.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The VFWF reserves the right to seek additional funds if the amount of the ____ is insufficient to fully meet the needs.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer ____ a health problem - it is a symptom of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "vague", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Once a language has less than about a hundred speakers, it is almost impossible to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "permit", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to allow", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you want to know whether an phrase is ____ or not, look it up in Google.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company directors are ____ that business will improve in the new year.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The committee was tasked to review the tests and criteria used to ____ visual disability for purposes of eligibility for health Insurance benefits.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "determine", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It circles the theater so that you can ____ projectors at any spot on the dome, whereas before we were limited to placing them toward the back of the room.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "aim", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Due to the severe ____ of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to assemble a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The data center will ____ researchers through the application of mathematics and computer science to biological problems.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you ____ against the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "UK airports have increased the ____ of security staff since the terrorist attacks in London.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These orders do much to ____ the significant need for better organization in terms of record-keeping.", "Opt_1": "resign", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "But, for their part, the Syrian leaders failed to ____ for Israel to have rights to some of that water.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "provoke", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to cause to happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government is considering whether to ____ smoking in all public places.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The new teacher looks quite young but his ____ age is 55.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not ____ to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or lack of exercise.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Attendance will not constitute a specific percentage of your final grade, but if you miss more than two classes you will ____ fail this course.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to ____ the secret until means have been found to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government generally did not take steps to ____ or punish the most serious cases of abuse.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very ____ that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at prior to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "confident", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "ideal", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lack of knowledge is not a suitable reason for failure to ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The best way to ensure that your machine has a unique name is to use your University ____ name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He also responded that his particular school did not ____ courses in English as a Second Language (ESL).", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is the single most important ____ a district judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ of weight change through pregnancy was similar across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "reply", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "an answer", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All this progress was a ____ of the advance of technology and also of advances in government and other social organizations in capitalist society.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "consequence", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ a list of the local doctors who can speak English.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I did not understand what the artist was trying to express by these two pieces, nor did I see any ____ in the work.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "skill", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "What is your ____ of his recent odd behaviour?", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to provide a better ____ for people to save more of their money.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "San Francisco's justice reform program is ____ alive, says a UC Berkeley report.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the reasons for invading Iraq were to gain control of its oil.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need to devise a test to ____ the improvement in ESL students' English from one year to the next.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is a highly ____ view of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While we were not ____ surprised by the answers to our questions, it was interesting to see the amount of uniformity in answers.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although the patient was in pain, the doctor did not ____ the problem as serious.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to ____ him to make a sound decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "utter", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "complete, total"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The fact that he can only speak a little English is sure to ____ his already severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Before having a ____ surgical procedure patients must always consent.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "People are more likely to take risks they would not take when sober, and are unable to ____ accurately their ability to drive.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One of the major goals of Women's Studies over the past 25 years has been to ____ the work of women writers from past times.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "share", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange; to give"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The first principle of this school is that all nationalities and cultures are equally important, even if some are more represented than others ____ the body of students.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Nancy Tsai knew from ____ that the housing situation for graduate students living off campus was bleak.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is ____ a surprise that national governments have failed to solve global problems, since they have also failed to solve their own domestic problems.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the ____ stage of education have insufficient alternative educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "new"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We reserve the right to refuse alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide ____ identification.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Therefore, if a farm has efficiency problems, simply expanding the operation may just ____ the problems.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a result of the efforts over this last year, SAGE was able to ____ books to more than 30 deserving schools in Illinois.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a ____ of student work in the corridor outside of the cafeteria.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These poems ____ a good grade, but because you gave them in late I have to give you a 0.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is yet to ____ basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. instead of He does ...", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "raise", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Not everyone is ____ enough to have internet access at home.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "fortunate", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "fortunate", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "lucky", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Government agencies and aid organizations often failed to ____ people in affected communities about aid distribution and reconstruction.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school plans to ____ the sports field so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ resulted in a statistic that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India ____ cars.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will ____ the carpet if you come inside with those dirty shoes.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Forests are both an important part of the ____ ecosystem and an important resource of raw materials for lumber, paper, and fuelwood.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "But please keep in mind that the Internet doesn't ____ career counseling.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her writing was poor in every respect; it was difficult to ____ her biggest problem.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "isolate", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to separate something or someone from others"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An abundance of research documents the biased and harsh treatment that Black defendants have received at the hands of ____ White jurors.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Emma was ____ of these various and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He came to the conclusion that Mexico's constitutions did not last because they ____ did not conform to Mexico's customs and traditions.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to ____ with it.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While the system has offered men the opportunity to become owners of small factories, this opportunity rests on the unpaid ____ of female family members.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I want to ____ you that I shall be leaving the school at the end of the next term.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He has lost the desire to consider what is right and wrong because he was hurt, ____ devastated, when the love of his life disappeared.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This book provides the definitive ____ of the origins of coffee drinking.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police are looking for a woman of ____ height, last seen wearing a red jacket.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The police had difficulty in trying to ____ the enormous crowd after the pop concert.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is an opportunity to pursue a more demanding curriculum while having an equal opportunity to ____ in the full benefits of university life.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "maintain", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "ESL teachers often ask their students to ____ words in class.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an ____ war, trying to conceal the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Yoo Jong-pil, spokesman of the DP, claimed Roh wanted to further ____ himself from the previous government and humiliate the DP.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Rules do not usually stimulate creativity or passion; ____ they demand conformity and make us fear change.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You have one last opportunity to show that you can work hard and ____ properly. If you don't take it, you will be asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The latest employment figures contradict the government's recent ____ that more people now have jobs than for many years.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The headmaster called a meeting to try to ____ the dispute between the two teachers.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "encourage", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "approach", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to near; to get closer"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school gave a ____ warning to the teacher who had arrived late to school several times that month.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our committee was asked to make recommendations to reduce the friction between teachers, parents and students, and ____ the three-way partnership.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "produce", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or create", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Can you please explain the ____ by which students are placed in ESL class?", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "principle", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government will ____ its announcement until it has up-to-date information.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done regarding the comparison of online ____ delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The reporter is interested in the proportion of ____ school teachers who have at least 20 years of experience.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government refused to ____ from its plan to ban smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "diverge", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you don't receive search results within that time frame or if this an ____ request, please contact the reference desk.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They ____ their nutrients from the air and not from the plant on which they are growing.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most ____ animal class is the insect. Insects come in thousands of shapes and colors.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "broad", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "wide, extensive"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Can you please give me the final ____ of your writing? This looks like your first draft before you corrected the spelling and grammar.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "environment", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "the world around us", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to try and ____ your thoughts a little more clearly. This does not make much sense to me.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They have made a ____ error in the way they are thinking about the opportunities and problems their business face.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "subjective", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Another common meaning of ____ is the date on something has to be done, as in Don't forget. Your project is ____ tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people think that the government ____ to reduce teenage pregnancy will not be successful.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We ____ outside counsel to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students gain professional ____ before graduation so that they enter the job market with a distinct advantage.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "contribute", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and considerable discontent has arisen ____ the Indians on account of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to ____ its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ failed to persuade workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your password should ____ only letters or numbers.", "Opt_1": "contain", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "List the specific things you did to ____ strong performance in your project.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "discern", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I'm not sure how to define any of these abstract terms, and yet I ____ some of the components of forgiveness.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We still don't know if this is really the correct mechanism to ____ the imbalance between matter and antimatter that we observe.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Can you please ____ that you will be at the school next year?", "Opt_1": "suffer", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She found that the document had no detail and conflicted with the assessments of ____ intelligence.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Looking up all the key words in an important passage should be considered a ____ check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The format for references must ____ to the guidelines in the approved style manual.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government must continue to make every ____ to prevent young people from becoming addicted to drugs.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to ____ what is happening in Afghanistan, it is necessary to go there yourself.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an ____ event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was ____ that the business would fail. It was badly run, and the products it sold were overpriced and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "AOL has said that this is a very dangerous virus and that there is NO ____ for it at this time.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Collecting information with no ____ plan or purpose and then hoping to transform it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "These results suggest that being treated as a sex ____ can undermine women's performance in stereotypically masculine domains.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "province", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows prior to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Unlike the clouds on Earth, however, many of the forms of interstellar clouds are completely ____ to the human eye.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you work harder, you will ____ a better grade next term.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "TOEFL is not the most ____ part of the application, but it is an unavoidable part, which sometimes can be quite painful and time- consuming.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "ordinary", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a thorough analysis, ____ it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of American voters have turned against the war in Iraq but not against the American troops and not against patriotism.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Catherwood Library is the most ____ resource of its type in North America.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to ____ a photograph when you apply for a job.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "fail", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree with the ____ that the earth is getting warmer because of human pollution.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Digital television is not yet ____ in many parts of the country.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that there is an abundant ____ of oil waiting to be discovered at the bottom of deep oceans.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What is absent in your essay is any reference to the ____ of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "society", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The assessment was not ____ of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the final report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola prior to its release.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a ____ difference between the sports of mountain-climbing and table tennis. In the first you can get killed; in the second usually not.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some of the ____ personal resources that you will draw from include your own academic background, teaching style, life experience, and technical experience.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "arbitrary", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "However, because The Dream intends to interest both lay and professional readers, it is unfortunate that she failed to ____ a glossary of significant terms.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "append", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She did not follow the directions on the label, ____ carefully reading it.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Musicians are listed alphabetically, but for some ____ reason Carter, Benny is listed after Carter, Ron.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "royal", "Opt_4": "odd", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_4_def": "strange, unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a bold idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the ____ arts.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's hard to ____ the temptation to buy from an unknown company when they're advertising low prices for name brand products.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If two students are always talking in class, then the teacher will often ____ them and make them sit in opposite parts of the room.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "abandon", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They would not fill their barrels when the captain told them, but instead, ran the ____ that there would be water ahead.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Three teachers are going to ____ at the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Distance learning is the most significant ____ occurring in higher education today.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "member", "Answer": "phenomenon", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I think the students enjoy the fact that they have the liberty to try different things, says Harris. You can ask them to ____ and see which direction they take.", "Opt_1": "expand", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm ____ was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "definitely", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a lively ____ in the country at the moment on whether cannabis should be made legal or not.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of the school behind the car park is for seniors only.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To ____ your head while mountain biking, you should wear a helmet.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Future research would need to ensure that participants did not engage in any other activities immediately ____ to the study at hand.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the ____ that best fits local facilities and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is usually a close ____ between students of the same nationality at an international school.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The most significant risk factor in predicting whether a person will ____ a violent crime in the future is whether the person has previous offenses.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "That is no way to ____ yourself in the library.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There would seem a ____ chance that the United States, working with the United Nations, will lead a worldwide religious revival.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The strategy used for the actual campaign was ____ different.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can exert sufficient ____ on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ goal of teaching is to teach students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will ____ its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a profound ____ on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is set to suffer a heavy ____ in the vote to approve its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete against the firms from not ____ India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Groups should advise the instructor if a ____ is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is fair to praise the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment ____ older people.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Only the one that meets the necessary and ____ conditions will win the election.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "available", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His examination failure did not ____ through lack of effort or ability but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The report shows how the mass media ____ affect adolescent smoking rates.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Your target heart ____ is a useful way of pacing yourself during exercise.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school have employed some guards to make the campus more ____ against unannounced visitors.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "by terrorists lies in the countries that possess such devices.", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To accommodate the great power ____ now rapidly occurring in Asia, the United States needs vigorous preparation by its executive branch and Congress.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For some observers, globalization is a terrible ____ and for others a wonderful world of possibilities and innovation.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to participate in the concept and ____ of marriage.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The demand for oil is ____ to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A common ____ in the English classroom is to classify the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is unable to ____ that Iran is planning to build nuclear weapons.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "prove", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Modern computers can store the ____ of many millions of pages of writing.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are more ____ to get a better grade if you check your work carefully.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It's always better to be ____ cautious and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Insurance salesmen often ____ profits that they know are very unlikely.", "Opt_1": "conceal", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to hide", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity ____ topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you are an ____ with a permanent disability, you may be eligible to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "bias", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is not a business. Its goal is not to make a large profit, but to earn enough money to ____ the best possible education.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I assume his strange behaviour ____ is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "recently", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "in the near past", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She says she's not a very good pianist, but I know that the ____ is true and she's just being modest.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You must consider how much it is going to cost and whether you really need it The government should consider the effects of its proposal on ____ people.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The producer of these webpages has long been an ____ of the value of computers in language teaching.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students should not ____ others of cheating unless there is clear evidence.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Not everyone knows that Texas was once a ____ of Mexico.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Our new system for handling lost ____ makes it possible for you to report the loss of belongings via Internet, on the telephone or at the counter.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The only goal of some people is to ____ as much money as possible.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Don't ____ me in your plan - I want nothing to do with it.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "facilitate", "Opt_4": "precede", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_4_def": "to go or be before someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ his plans for an industrial area, which he purchased from the Israel Land Administration.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There was little ____ that the government's plans to increase taxes would be very unpopular.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "doubt", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Governments are considering how to exploit the ____ mineral resources buried under the ice in Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "rational", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "vast", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The board was unable to ____ a candidate in the first round because of disagreement over candidates' performance.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "repeat", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the ____ community to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "They ____ that they did the work independently of each, but I don't believe them.", "Opt_1": "compete", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to ____ the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "measure", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "recover", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to get back", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can ____ a massive loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, ____ is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many countries have a ____ wage - this is the smallest amount of money that people may earn for a full-time job.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This situation is certain to improve over the next few years, given the ____ of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A serious problem of nuclear power is where and how to ____ of the radioactive waste.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are ____ parts of the planet that have not yet been explored. These are all on the ocean floor.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The powerful hold that the empire of Egypt had on Palestine at this time would not have permitted the rise of a significant ____ such as Israel.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company does a ____ amount of business in the USA; the majority of its trade is in Europe.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We should never praise or ____ any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She needed to ____ enough money to be able to afford London's sky-high prices.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, ____ is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In an era of privatisation and market rule we are facing the fact that ____ments will have to ____ a bit more.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "govern", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Is this a ____ picture by Picasso or is it a fake?", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is a controversial ____ that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is slightly down from the 19 percent failure ____ last year but still significantly above the failure ____ in other freshmen subjects.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My goal this ____ is to improve my mathematics and science grades.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors ____ that the better way to get and stay healthy is to eat lots of fruit and vegetables and take regular exercise.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I gave you ____ instructions not to open the box. Why did you disobey me?", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "commercial", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "to do with business", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What is the next letter in the ____ O, T, F, S, N, E, _?", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We must reverse the ____ of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Our preliminary surveys did not differentiate between different types of questions, so we were unable to ____ this issue.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can submit your work at any time ____ to the due date.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The donors specified that they would like to help hardworking students with ____ grades who deserve help.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "medium", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Without a filter on perceptual input, our brains would have the impossible task of sifting through an overload of information to ____ important from unimportant information.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "generate", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police were unable to ____ the demonstrators from the town square.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over ____ regulation of railroads was the chief issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "effort", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used force to ____ food.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Government scientists have found some red areas on the ____ of Jupiter, but they do not know yet what these signify.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The website shows how schools ____ and use their resources.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She ____ that the document had no detail and conflicted with the assessments of military intelligence.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "expose", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "AOL has said that this is a very dangerous virus and that there is NO ____ for it at this time.", "Opt_1": "priority", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "event", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The chairman needs to ____ a better meeting next time. The last one was very disorganized.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to ____ improve the quality of laser light at extremely short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school established a ____ to discuss the introduction of a bilingual programme.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What would you ____ to do today? Write a dictation or watch a video?", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "improve", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The difficulties that ____ from time to time in the business can be solved by good management.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are an individual with a permanent disability, you may be ____ to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company's efforts to increase business over the past year failed to ____ the shareholders.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Farmers ____ their crops. This means that they do not grow the same thing on the same field for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "provoke", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "rotate", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the item did not acknowledge the ____ developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "positive", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "medium", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "in the middle", "Opt_4_def": "small"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She has continued ____ me with her hard work and positive attitude.", "Opt_1": "allocate", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ collection is complete and available for online access.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the ____ between North and South campuses with two concerts that combine symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "gap", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They will have to live without their family ____ for the rest of their life due to this terrible form of cancer and they will deserve to be compensated.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Today we will practise for the ____ test.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Janice Walker wanted to examine further ways to continue this great ____ to the company's staff as well as the company's productivity.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is beyond the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the ____ will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a ____ loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Under the new plan, the garden would remain at its current ____ on Walnut and Virginia streets and the pumping station would be built on the northeast.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ solution to this problem would be for everyone to say sorry and then just forget the whole thing.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We also want to speak openly about the question of whether the German radio should ____ so-called jazz music.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school decided to retreat when the angry parent said that he would ____ his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "ruin", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There will be an ____ of 20 minutes in the middle of the school play.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students needed to ____ considerable time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students post messages and ____ ideas through the bulletin board.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Illegal immigration is not the ____ reason so many poor young blacks are on the streets and why some turn to gangs, guns and drug dealing.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I am often surprised by the ____ of some high school students. One of them yesterday did not know the name of the president of the USA.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He did not ____ to one set of religious beliefs and pioneered a new artistic style known today as symbolism.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school will ____ use of the library for all students unless the student who damaged the photocopier is found.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government's priority in his second ____ of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government tried hard to ____ its decision, but most people believe it was a serious error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your English is ____ improving, but you'll have to make greater effort if you want to get better more quickly.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What's the meaning of the ____ hypothesis?", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School needs to ____ its curriculum with that of German state schools.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The internet allows people to ____ whatever they want without needing to go to the shops.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An international school is a place that cannot survive if there is prejudice that ____ groups of students are better than others.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "probable", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Everyone knows that smoking and drinking heavily is not a ____ way to live but some are addicted and cannot stop.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is ____ true in the environmental sciences where many of the systems are dynamic and extremely complex.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This unnecessary ____ would adversely impact the existing review system that ensures the high quality of scientific research in the United States.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has set a clear ____ on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the atmosphere every year.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are an individual with a permanent disability, you may be ____ to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "eligible", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Hydrogen has the ____ to provide a clean, storable, transportable and renewable source of energy that can meet the need for power throughout the world.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company yesterday said it made a ____ of \ufffd\ufffd217.46 million for the six months to June.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There are ____ any teachers at the school who cannot speak at least two languages.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The committee will investigate the ____ by which the decision was made.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Colorado State University scientists have found a way to dramatically improve the quality of laser light at ____ short wavelengths.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A typical problem is that many companies will only employ workers with experience, but how do young people ____ that experience if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Due to the money ____ in schools, teachers are now being charged a high fee for training.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school's decision to raise the tuition fees will have a serious ____ on the number of students who plan to attend.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "implication", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "implication", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Patients are ____ to forget information that is not written down.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "African-Americans have disproportionately failed to ____ in American society.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is possible to ____ the world by boat in about three days.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it reliable and ____ decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not force us to ____ the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "reduce", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Because of the interactive nature of the classroom, absences will significantly ____ your performance in the course.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I do not wish to ____ that she is lazy, but her work is often late and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The main ____ of a teacher is to teach.", "Opt_1": "exponent", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government intends to ____ the information for itself. The public will not have access to it until the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "persist", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is the single most important deed a ____ judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "behalf", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government would like to reform the health service but the doctors are ____ their proposals.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the impulse to improve his ____ poor grades.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Administrators and supervisors are expected to see that those who report to them are informed about, understand and ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In Germany most students have the chance to ____ practical experience in an office or factory, before deciding what job they would like to do.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "status", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "position, standing", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course is intended to ____ a lot of class discussion.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government will ____ its announcement until it has up-to-date information.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a highly subjective view of the symbolic nature of ____ reality.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I find it very difficult to ____ his bad manners.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These notes are intended as a ____ introduction to some of the main ideas and methods of calculus.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is essential that governments take counsel before making the ____ to go to war.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The referee of a football match can ____ the offside flag of his or her linesman.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ between mother and child is said to be the strongest of any personal relationships.", "Opt_1": "tradition", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Despite the enormous amount of effort invested in her language teaching she was not able to ____ grammatical sentences.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "\"Recommended Changes to Student Handbook\" was the next ____ for discussion.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A foreigner who wants to become a ____ of the USA cannot have a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The topic of child deaths in the nineteenth century is one which could ____ fail to interest any serious scholar of the period.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "One ____ of the internet that concerns many parents and teachers is that a huge amount of very offensive material is just a click away.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Niehuss does much to ____ the enormous impact of consumer culture on West German women's lives.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main objective of the proposed ____ is to investigate the influence of West African languages.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The need for regulation is quite evident today but was not ____ before the early years of the 20th century.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "As ancient pottery workers experimented with the effects of higher temperatures on ceramics, they began to develop methods to ____ a high enough temperature that copper could be melted.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic growth was ____ and its benefits were widely spread throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "rapid", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "quick", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government was fully aware of the ____ of its decision to go to war.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}]]